(Penny:)There you go.
You're all done!
(Amy:)That wasn't so bad.
(inhales delightedly)
(Amy:)Nice.
(Amy:)Boy, if my mom could see me now,
(Amy:)she'd lock me in the sin closet.
(Bernadette:)That's a joke, right?
(Amy:)Actually, the joke was on her.
(Amy:)I could still see the TV
through the slats.
(Penny:)I'm starting to see
(Penny:)why you and your mom
aren't very close.
(Bernadette:)Bet she'd still tell her
(Bernadette:)if she got married.
(Penny:)You're not gonna
let this go, are you?
(Amy:)Well, it's kind of sad
that they don't know.
(Amy:)I mean, they love Leonard.
(Penny:)Fine, you want
me to call?
(Penny:)I'll call.
(exhales)
(Penny:)Why am I so nervous?
(Bernadette:)It's understandable.
(Bernadette:)Amy was afraid to tell her mom
she broke up with Sheldon.
(Penny:)Yeah?
How did it go?
(Penny:)Did she make you crawl
(Penny:)into the breaking-up drawer?
(Amy:)Uh, well, actually,
to be honest...
I-I haven't told her yet.
(Penny:)You've been giving me
a hard time
(Penny:)and you haven't even told
your mom about Sheldon?
(Amy:)I'm feeling a little dizzy
from all the blood loss.